createafreewebsite.net 2006-04-19

# Privacy Statement - Create Free Websites

How do you use single-pixel gifs? 

Said and its advertisers may use single-pixel gif images, sometimes referred to as web bugs or web beacons, to count Web page accesses and gather some general statistical information. Said does not gather personal information through the use of these images. Our advertisers may use single-pixel gifs that can track personal information from cookies that may have been previously placed on a user's computer by an advertiser. 

What information do you collect when I register for something? 

Said offers access to services that are free but that require registration. We will use your registration contact information to send notification of Said products and services by e-mail and/or postal mail. We also may share that information with our clients. Our clients may send you promotional material that is related to the topic of the service for which you registered unless you have chosen not to receive it. Said reserves the right to send to our registered members email notices and announcements that may be of interest to Said users. TO NOT RECEIVE ANY COMMUNICATION FROM Said , MEMBERS SHOULD REQUEST THAT THEIR REGISTRATION BE CANCELLED AND AGREE NOT TO USE ANY FREE Said SERVICES. For further clarification of this policy, contact us by email at concerns@said.com. 

What other information do you request? 

We will most likely also request your e-mail address or mailing address and other personal information for the purposes of providing additional services (for example, subscriptions to e-mail newsletters, announcement lists or information about seminars). Whenever we request the identity of a visitor, we will clearly indicate the purpose of the inquiry before the information is requested. We maintain a strict "No-Spam" policy that means that we do not intend to sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third-party, without your consent. We may from time to time send e-mail announcing new Said products and services. By using services on Said Web Sites, you are agreeing we can send you this email. If you choose to supply your postal address in an online form, you may receive mailings from other third party companies. 

Will you disclose the information you collect to outside third parties? 

Said will disclose personal information and/or an IP address, when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities or comply with legal process served on Said , Protect and defend the rights or property of the Said Network of Sites and related properties, or visitors to the Said Network of Sites and related properties, Identify persons who may be violating the law, the Said Web site User Agreement, the rights of third parties, or otherwise misusing the Said Network or its related properties. Said uses reasonable precautions to keep the information disclosed to us secure. Said reserves the right to transfer all such information in connection with the sale of all or part of Said 's capital stock or assets. Furthermore, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information. We are not responsible for such third party privacy policies or how they treat information about their users 

## Opt-in announcement List Privacy Policy 

As an added benefit to the visitors of the Said Network of sites, we have a relationship with Said, an independent third party company that sends e-mail announcements to individuals who request to receive them. When you register you are given the opportunity to also receive announcement lists from Said. Whether you want to receive these announcement lists is your choice; you should only receive those lists you affirmatively choose to. If you choose to receive a specific announcement list, you will receive commercial messages that are related to the topic of the list from independent third parties that have contracted with Said and/or Saidto send messages to the list. Personally identifiable information will not be used by Said or Saidfor any purposes other than to deliver the e-mail announcements. You may stop the arrival of these announcement lists at any time by removing your e-mail address from the list by forwarding the announcement list to deleteall@said.com, or by following the instructions on the e-mails you receive. 

What else should I know about my privacy when online? 

The Said Network of Web sites contains many hyperlinks to other Web sites and from Affiliate Web sites. The Said Web Sites also contain advertisements of third parties. Said is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites or advertisers. Said does not share any of the individual personal information you provide Said with the Web sites to which Said links, except as stated elsewhere within this Privacy Policy, although Said may share aggregate data with such Web sites (such as how many people use our Site). Your Consent To This Agreement By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by Said and agree to receive communications from Said as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Please send any questions about Said �s Privacy Policy to: concerns@said.com
